{
    "subject": "resource/Pained",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Films_based_on_South_Korean_comics",
    "human_readable": "Pained is the subject of films based on South Korean comics.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7562836408615112,
            "question": "Can you give examples of films based on South Korean comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7354376316070557,
            "question": "Is there a trend of adapting South Korean comics into films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6912789344787598,
            "question": "What type of stories are films based on South Korean comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.686130166053772,
            "question": "What is a common theme in films based on South Korean comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669100821018219,
            "question": "Are there films adapted from South Korean comics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5186387896537781,
            "question": "What makes South Korean comics appealing for film adaptations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46118173003196716,
            "question": "Where do South Korean comics originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2533576786518097,
            "question": "How popular are South Korean comics internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19547930359840393,
            "question": "Which country's comics inspire films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1585116684436798,
            "question": "What is the source material for some films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pained is the subject of films based on South Korean comics.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country's comics inspire films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How popular are South Korean comics internationally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where do South Korean comics originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5130_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions several movies and their relation to South Korean comics, such as \"Pain (2011)\" and \"The Webtoon (2013)\". This supports the statement that films are based on South Korean comics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Text 4 states Kangfull movies bought the rights to \"Pain\" before the comic was finished, they even hired him to write the screenplay. The fact that he decided he was happy with the script and never made the comic implies a film based on it already exists.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}